Guide to the Church Coalition for Human Rights in the Philippines records, 1982-1993.
Church Coalition for Human Rights in the Philippines records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Church Coalition for Human Rights in the Philippines records, 1982-1993.
4913
Church Coalition for Human Rights in the Philippines.
41 cubic ft.
Organizational records, correspondence, printed materials, and photographs
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Subject files, correspondence, minutes, case files, pamphlets, booklets, photographs, and other collected papers of a human rights group.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Subject files, correspondence, minutes, case files, pamphlets, booklets, photographs, and other collected papers of a human rights group. Other rights groups are mentioned frequently, and files were kept on many individuals.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Church Coalition for Human Rights in the Philippines.
Subjects:
Human rights -- Philippines.; Human rights -- Religious aspects.; Human rights advocacy -- Philippines.; Church and social problems -- Philippines.; Church and state -- Philippines.; Christianity and the social sciences -- Philippines.; Christianity and the social sciences; Church and social problems; Church and state; Human rights; Human rights advocacy; Human rights -- Religious aspects
Places:
Philippines
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Maria Sabido, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 1)
- E. San Juan, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 2)
- SCM-NESC-S, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 3)
- SCM-Student Christian Movement, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Fr. Orlando Tizon, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 5)
- T.W. Labor and US Law, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Ruth Harris, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Chair-Ruth M. Harris, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 8)
- CCHRP subcommittee on Advocacy/Congress Work, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 9)
- CCHRP subcommittee on Constituency Education, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Treasurers: Reverend S. Michael Hahm, Fr. Mike O'Loughlin, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Wilsons, Paul/Dede, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Ed Luidens, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Richard Deats, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 14)
- GSP/Labor, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 15)
- December 1983 Key Contact mailing, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Originals of primers/brochures etc, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 17)
- February 1984 PHIDOC Mailing, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- PHIDOC (no. 4 and 5), Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Subcommittee Hearing Sen. Benigno Auino 11/18/81 Aquino, 1981-11-18 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Subcommittee Hearing Sen. Benigno Auino 11/18/81 Aquino, 1981-11-18 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Subcommittee Hearing Sen. Benigno Auino 11/18/81 Aquino, 1981-11-18 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Bill C., Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Sr. Stella Bates, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Diokno, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Sr. Mary "Mayang" Grenough, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Carol Heise, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Bishop Labayen, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Salvador Laurel, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Mangalapus-MFP, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Ernie Rondon, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Dante Simbulon, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 32)
- CCHRP subcommittee on Finance, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 33)
- CCHRP subcommittee on Nominations, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Networking Newsletter-(churches) January 1984, 1984-01 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Newsletter, 1984-07 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- National Security (State) - Philippines Doctrine, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 37)
- International Justice Network (USCMA), Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Asia-Pacific Groups in Washington DC, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Media Contacts, Telex to the Philippines: Cardinal Sin, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Resource List/Materials, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Statements/Petitions/etc, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Originals of Response Letters and Resolutions and Statements etc, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Subscriptions-Phil, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Layout for print, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Telex from the Philippines, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Visitors to the US: Fr. Ed De La Torre, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Jimmy Tan, M.D., Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Fr. Jose Dizon, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 50)
- 1985-Phil. Visitors, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Florchita Bautista, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Sr. Rosario, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Sr. Mary John Mananzan, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Ernie Arellano visit, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Fr. Ralph Kroes, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Claver, Visit, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 57)
- India, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Central America, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Regional Council on Human Rights (Asia), Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 60)
- DND Information kit, Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Commission on HR (PHILGON), Date unknown (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Ecumenical Evaluation, 1990-01 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Team-Visit to the Philippines on the Situation of Internal Refugees - Church World Service - NCCCUSA
- The Iceberg and the Cross AMRSP (processed), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- EXODUS International Fact Finding Mission Nov. 1989 (processed), 1989-11 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Statistical Summaries, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Testimonies and Stories, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 3)
- The Church and Human rights, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 4)
- TFD, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Conc. Paper
- Editorials, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 6)
- HURIDOCS, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Ramsey Clark Fact Finding Reports, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Hist. Docs.
- 90 Political Prisoners, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- 90 Families Fleeing War, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- 90 Cafgu and Vigilantes, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- 90 Women, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- 90 Negros, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Reg. Rep'ts
- 90 Northern Luzon, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- 1990 Surigao Del Sur, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- 1990 Zamboanga Del Sur, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Davao City, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 16)
- UCCP HR, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Persecution, Other Cases 1991
- Cullen, Fr. Shay, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Statistical Summaries, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Warrantless Arrest, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Warrantless Arrest Ruling, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- 91-1 CCHRP UA, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- 91-2 CCHRP UA, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- 91-3 CCHRP UA, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- 91-4 CCHRP UA, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- 91-5 CCHRP UA, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- 91-6 CCHRP UA, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- TDFP Task Force Detainees Philippines, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  91 TFD UA HR Orgs
- Cordillera Resource Center, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- EMJP Ecumenical Movement for Justice and Peace, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Health, Medical Action Group, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- 91 Committee To Protect Journalists, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Center for Community Health Services, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- 91 Asia Watch Report, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- 91 Ohio Coalition for Philippine Concerns, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- 91 CUANES UA, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- 91 Amnesty International UA, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Cases A-D, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Cases E-H, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Cases I-L, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Cases M-P, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Cases Q-T, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Cases U-Z, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- 91-2 Augusto Tupas, 1990-11-30-1991 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- 91-1 Fr. Pico, 1991-01-10 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- 91-3 Melland and Rosella Dilodilo, 1990-10-26-1991 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Fr. Rex Mannsman, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Fr. Nerlito Satur, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- 91 "Other" Cases, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- 91-4 Political Prisoners, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Marag valley AFP Operations, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  Counter Insur. -LIC
- Marag valley AFP Operations, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- 91 Church Persecution, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Regional Reports, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Jack Walsh Updates, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  91 Mindanao
- Testimonies and Stories, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Correspondence: Human Rights, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Statistical Summaries, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- 90-1 CCHRP UA, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- 90-2 CCHRP UA, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- 90-3 CCHRP UA, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- 90-4 CCHRP UA, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- 90-5 CCHRP UA, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- 90-6 CCHRP UA, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- 90-7 CCHRP UA, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- 90-8 CCHRP UA, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- 90-9 CCHRP UA, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- 90 TFD UA, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- PAHRA/EMJP, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 65)
- 90 NECP UA, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  HROrgs
- 90-Cum CUANES UA, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- 90 Amnesty International UA, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- 90 MIPCS UA, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Human Rights Urgent Action Addresses, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Lawyer's Committee on Human Rights, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 71)
- 90 Asia Watch Report, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- 90 Com. To Protect Journalists: CPJ Report (processed), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Misc. Action Alerts 1990, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- 90-1 Loberio, N. and Abawag, D. Abduct., 1990 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  Case Documents
- 90-2 Guzman, Loiue de (L) Abduct., 1990 (Box 2, Folder 75)
- 90- Loenidas, Wilson (UP) Abduct., 1990 (Box 2, Folder 76)
- 90-1 Death Penalty, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 77)
- Fr. Shay Cullen, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Schmitz, Fr. Carl UPDATE, Date unknown (Box 2, Folder 79)
  Individual Cases
- 90 Villalba, Noel UPDATE, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 80)
- 90-5 Tadao, Jaime (P) IL Arrest, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 81)
- Statistical Summaries (PAHRA), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- US State Dept. of Human Rights Report, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 2)
- A-D, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- E-H, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- I-L, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Amnesty International, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Human Rights Organizations
- AAAS Science and Human Rights, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 7)
- DAGA, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Canada-Asia Working Group, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 9)
- NCCP, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 10)
- A-D, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Individual Human Rights Cases
- E-H, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- I-L, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- M-P, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Q-T, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- U-Z, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Christopher Batan, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 16)
- James Rowe US Military, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Communal Human Rights Cases and follow up Human Rights Cases, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- CUANES-CCHRP Transition, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Misc. Correspondence
- Political Prisoners Statistics, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous Human Rights, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 21)
- UA CCHRP 93-3, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- UA CCHRP 93-2, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- UA CCHRP 93-1, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- TFDP, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Satur Ocampo TFDP Campaign for Release, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  Political Prisoner campaign
- Satur Ocampo TFDP Campaign for Release, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- UN world conference on Human Rights, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Statistical Summaries, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- UA CCHRP 92 Letters of Response, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- 92-1 CCHRP UA, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- 92-2 CCHRP UA, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- 92-3 CCHRP UA, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- 92-4 CCHRP UA, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- 92-5 CCHRP UA, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- 92-6 CCHRP UA, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- TFDP 92, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- M-P 92, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Q-T 92, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- U-Z 92, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Fr. Salvatore Carteza Italian Priest Killed, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Fr. Peter Geremia et. al., Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Misc. Human Rights Cases, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Follow Up Human Rights Cases, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Misc. Correspondence, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 45)
- SELDA Class action vs. Marcos, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 46)
- PAX CHRISTI USA (The Negros Action Alert), Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 47)
- CUANE-Phil., Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 48)
- PAHRA, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 49)
- AMRSP, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 50)
- TABAK, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 51)
- AAAS Science and Human Rights, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 52)
- FIND, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 53)
- PDF, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Philippine International Forum, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Political Prisoners Stats (National), 1992 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- 92 Luzon, political prisoners stats, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- 92 Visayas, political prisoners stats, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- 92 Mindanao, political prisoners stats, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- 92 National Capital Region, political prisoners stats, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Human Rights Mis., Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 61)
- 702nd Brigade-PA Sagada, Mt. Province, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Women, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Teacher's Strike, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Mt. Apo, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Counter Insurgency - LIC "Total War", Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 66)
  Militarization
- CAFGU'S Vigilantes, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 67)
- NPA - Surigao Ambush, 1992-02-15 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Military Operations, Date unknown (Box 3, Folder 69)
- HR docs extras, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Steering Committee Minutes, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
- Steering Committee Minutes, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
- Steering Committee Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
- Network Mailings, 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- CCHRP, AMRSP, NCCP, CONTAK Consultation, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Action Plan, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Steering Committee Communication, Date unknown (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Papers to read per April 11, 1990 meeting, 1990-04-11 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- CCHRP Networking Committee, Date unknown (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Steering Committee Minutes and Memos, Date unknown (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Steering Committee Retreat, 1991-05-31-1991-06-02 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Human Rights Cases (A-Z), Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 1-25)
- Urgent Action, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Responses to HR Urgent Action, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Urgent Action (Human Rights Violations), Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Letters to American Companies, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Response to Congress Alert, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Political Prisoner List, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Preventative Detention Action, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 32)
- List of Prisoners Released Still Detained, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Disappearances, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Presidential Decrees, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 35)
- The Phil Church and People's Struggles, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Fr. Zacharias Agatep, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Church Martyrs: Sumanil, Osorio, Beling, Bernardo, Romero, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Karl Gaspar, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Fr. Pete Lucero, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Negroes Nine -- Gore, BCC, etc, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Fr. Teodoro Remigio, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Yolanda Gordula, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Isagani Serrano, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Bobby de la Paz, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Hilda Narciso, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Lean Alejandro, J.V. Bautista and Boni de Luna, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Mila Aguilar, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Miscellaneous Cases, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Adora Faye De Vera, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Fr. Rudy Romano, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Samar Raid, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Fr. Orlando Tizon, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Fr. Tullio Favali, 1985-04-11 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Unlabeled (Reverend Antonio Fortich), Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Corazon C. Aquino - Profiles, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Jose Ma. Sison, etc, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Max L. Stackhouse, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Si Christine Tan RGS, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Jose W. Diokno, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Min Juan Ponce Enrile, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Charito Planas, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Jaime Cardinal Sin, Date unknown (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Statistican Summaries, Date unknown (Box 6, Folder 1)
- 89 UA (Urgent Action/requests/responses), 1989 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- 89 UA (Urgent Action/requests/responses), 1989 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- 89 UA (Urgent Action/requests/responses), 1989 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- 89 UA (Urgent Action/requests/responses), 1989 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- 89 UA (Urgent Action/requests/responses), 1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- 89 UA (Urgent Action/requests/responses), 1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- 89 Gran, Rev. Vizminda CP, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- 89-10 REYALDO, Sandy AB/DIS, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- 89-2 Salway, Angus DET, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- 89-2 UCCP RRM to S. Cotobato Harrass, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- 89-11 Santa Clara and Llenaresas Disap., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- 89 Ecija Maddacre Update, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- 89-6 "Killing Fields", 1989 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- 89 Lupao Massacre Update, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- 89-4 Paombong Fish Pond Killings, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Other Cases, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- 89 Alforque, Fr. Benjamin Cp, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- 89 Castillo, Pastor Fred Cp, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- 89 Labayen, Bishop Julio x Cp, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- 89 Malalay, Fr. Dionisio cp, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- 89 Mansmann, Fr. Rex CO, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- 89 Negros: Death lists CP, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- 89 Ruelo Pastor Zenaldo, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- 89 Veraguas, Fred CP, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- 89 Vina, Pastor, Carlos CP, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- 89 Other Case: Ch Persecution, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- 89 Romano, Rudy. Favali Update, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- 89 Surigao, Att, Alfonso Update, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- 89 Oton, Winnie (Digos) Killed, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- 89 - Cum Pol Prisoners: Clippings PP, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- 89 - Cum Pol Prisoners: UA cases PP, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- 89 - Cum Pol Prisoners: TFD PP, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- 89 - 10 Salas, Rudy PP, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- 89 - 11 Pol. Prisoners: Listing PP, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- 89 Digos: CCHRP Action, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- 89 Digos: Key Documentation, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- 89 Digos: Misc. Statements/Corr., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- 89 Digos NDF Statements, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- 89 Digos NCCP Statements, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- 89 Digos: Religious Right Media, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- 89 Digos: UCCP Statements, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- 89 Digos: Misc. Clippings, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- 89 Digos: US media, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- 89 Mindanao - General, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- 89 Agusan Del Sur, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- 89 Surigao Del Sur, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- 89 Danao Del Norte, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- 89 Cotabato, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- 89 Zamboanga Del Sur, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- 89 Josefina, Zamboanga Del Sur, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- 89 N. Luzon cases, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- 89 Mt. Province Op. Pakilala, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- 89 Kalinga Apayao Op. Pakilala, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Visayas: Vida Files Visayas Human Development Agency, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Negros, Date unknown (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Negros-Operation Thunderbolt, Date unknown (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Senator Edward Kennedy, Date unknown (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Phil Desk - State Dept., Date unknown (Box 7, Folder 2)
- State Department Human Rights Reports, Date unknown (Box 7, Folder 3)
- HOUSE COMMITTEE ON FOREIGN AFFAIRS: subcommittee on Asian and Pacific Affairs, Date unknown (Box 7, Folder 4)
- William Sullivan, David Joel Steinberg, 1982-09-28 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Carrles Greenleaf (AID), James Kelly of the Defense Dept., John Monio (State Dept), 1984-02-07 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Dr. Joel Steinberg, William Sullivan, Alex A. Esclamado, 1984-02-22 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- The Hall Amendment, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Earl Martin, 1983-05-10 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- HOUSE COMMITTEE ON APPROPRIATIONS: subcommittee on foreign operations, Date unknown (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Rev. Dr. Brouwer (NCCC-USA), Shoki Coe, 1982-09-23 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Asst. Sec. of State, Bishop Claver, Keesler, Manglapus, Ellsworth, Youngblood, 1982-09-21 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- HOUSE COMMITTEE ON FOREIGN AFFAIRS: subcommittee on Human Rights and international operations, Date unknown (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Marjorie Neihaus: "Philippines in Turmoil: Implications for US Policy", Date unknown (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Campaign for Political Rights, Date unknown (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Prof. Pyle, Waldemar Solf etc, 1982-07-22 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- HOUSE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE: subcommittee on crime, Date unknown (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Aquino, Lela Noble, P.W. Stanley, Danta Simbulan, 1983-06-28 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Admiral La Rocque, G. Kahin Lt. Col W. Berry etc., 1983-06-28 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Admiral Lon, P. Wolfitz, Hon. Armitage, 1983-06-16 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- National Lobby Day 84 (Campaign to oppose US aid), 1984 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous Statements, Date unknown (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous Statements, Date unknown (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Miscellaneous Statements, Date unknown (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Generalized System of Preferences, Date unknown (Box 7, Folder 25)
- PHRL Meetings / Minutes, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- PHRL Meetings / Minutes, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- PHRL, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- PHRL, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- PHRL, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Congress, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Testimony-House Foreign Affairs: Subcomm on Asia, 1992-03 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Congress, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- House Committee on Foreign Affairs, 1989-02-28 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Solarz Sub-committee Hearing, 1989-03-07 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Senate App for Op Hearing, Date unknown (Box 8, Folder 10)
- House For Affairs - Subcomm on Asia and Pacific-draft report, 1989-04-18 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Testimony - Public Witness Hearing, 1989-04-27 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Critique of 4/28/89 Report to Appropriations Comm of Senate and House, 1989-04-28 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Testimony by Seymour Helman before House Comm on Banking, Finance and Urb. Aff., Date unknown (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Testimony - for Op Subcommittee of the Sen For Ops Comm, 1989-07-11 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Lobby Day Report Forms, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Foreign Operations, Export Financing…Bill, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- US Information Agency, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- 1989 State Department Report on the Philippines (and CCHRP Response), 1989 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Correspondence with Sen and Reps, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Church's Cong Appeals, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Media Packet for Aquino visit Oct. 1989, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- PHRL Letter to senators and Reps from Religious Leaders, Cong Statements testimony etc, Date unknown (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Congressional office visits/feedback, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- NCCC-USA delegation materials, Date unknown (Box 8, Folder 25)
  Report, congressional briefing papers, etc
- Correspondence with Sen. and Reps, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- US State Dept., 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Miscellaneous Advocacy, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- PHRL - Senator Bob Dole, Date unknown (Box 8, Folder 29)
- PHRL - Senator John Kerry, Date unknown (Box 8, Folder 30)
- PHRL - Individual moc Senator Barbara Mikulski, Date unknown (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Rep Charles E Bennett, Date unknown (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Senate Budget Cite HRGS - Defece Budge, 1988-03-03 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Senate Appropriations Defece subctt, 1988-05-10 (Box 8, Folder 34)